(Sheldon:)there is a
gentleman caller
(Sheldon:)bringing flowers
to your fiancée as we speak.
(Leonard:)What?
(Leonard:)Why didn't you say that first?
(Sheldon:)Why didn't you get
extra peanut sauce?
(Sheldon:)We can both play this game.
(Leonard:)Can I help you?
(Man:)Oh, hi.
(Man:)Uh, does Penny live here?
(Leonard:)May I ask why?
(Man:)Well, uh...
I-I met her at my office,
she winked at me.
(Man:)And, uh...
I-I came hoping to initiate
a romantic relationship.
(Leonard:)Okay, um...
(Leonard:)Look, I'm pretty sure
she didn't wink at you.
(Man:)Oh, she did.
(Man:)Seductively, like this.
(Man:)And then she touched my arm
for two Mississippis.
(Man:)Like, you know,
one Mississippi, two...
(Leonard:)I got it, I got it.
(Leonard:)Listen, um...